chargemap.com 2014-12-02

# ChargeMap Privacy policies

[Home page](http://chargemap.com/ "Charging stations for electric vehicles") / [Support](http://chargemap.com/infos/chargemap) / [Legal information](http://chargemap.com/infos/legal)

## Legal information

Site publisher: The website ChargeMap.com is the property of: [SAABRE SARL](http://www.saabre.com/ "edition de sites web"), 104 rue de Hochfelden 67200 STRASBOURG FRANCE. 

SAABRE SARL, Publication director: Yoann NUSSMBAUMER  
Site designed by: SAABRE SARL  
Website host: Celeonet SARL, 55 rue Boissonade 75014 PARIS, FRANCE, which has the following phone number : +33 (0)1 40 64 01 32

## French Data Protection Act

The site publisher states that they automatically collect the personal data of the ChargeMap.com site users, in particular, the data provided when registering on the web site, or the data provided when contacting the site publisher.

By providing personal data, the user agrees to the automatic processing of personal data.

## Purpose

The personal data collected will essentially allow ChargeMap to know its visitors better and to inform them about the ChargeMap.com website.

They are intended for the site publisher, in charge of data processing, and to third parties that are established in or outside of the European Union. 

## Length

The personal data are stored for an indefinite period, and where necessary, until the User who has provided the personal data makes a request to remove the data.

## Mandatory Personal Data

When a User is providing personal data on the ChargeMap website, it is indicated by an asterisk whether the information is mandatory or optional.

If a User refuses to provide personal data when required to, they cannot send a form, or to contact the site publisher.

## Users rights

In compliance with French law, users whose personal data have been collected have the right to access their data and to request that the data be rectified, updated, or deleted by sending an email to the following address: contact@ChargeMap.com.

The information provided by users during their contributions become anonymous but will not be completely removed from ChargeMap.com in order not to prevent the smooth operation of the site.

## Cookies

We would like to leave a cookie on your computer. The cookie stores information about your use of our site (pages visited, date and time of the visit, etc.). We can read this information during future visits. The cookie are not intended to spy on your visits, but permits it to navigate on the site and for us to improve our services. It is indispensable for the smooth operation of ChargeMap.com.

This information can be stored for an unlimited period of time on your computer. The cookie does not enable a user to be identified personally.

You can decline storing cookies by configuring your browser in the following manner; however, this will prevent you from using all the features of the website:

### For Mozilla firefox:

Choose the "Tools" menu and then "Options"  
Click on the "Privacy" icon  
Choose the "Cookie" menu and select the options you wish. 

### For Microsoft Internet Explorer:

Choisissez le menu « Outils » (ou « Tools »), puis « Options Internet » (ou « Internet Options »).  
choose the "Tools" menu, then "Internet Options"  
click on the "Confidentiality" tab

### For Opéra:

Choose the "File" Menu > "Preferences"  
Privacy policy

## Newsletters

The site's publisher commits to asking for your consent before sending any newsletters. If you do not wish to receive any further newsletters, please go the appropriate page on the website ChargeMap.com.
